TAMARA STAMPONE

UX DESIGNER

™ tamarastampone@gmail.com



35 Halina Lane, Butler, NJ 07405

Behance.com/TScreativeUX

(973) 356-5246

tamarastampone.com

ABOUT ME

Self-driven Video Editor turned UX designer ready to use my analytical and creative mindset to solve problems and enhance user experiences. Starting my own business has allowed me to understand how users precieve information and empathsize with customers through visual designs. I strive to always better myself and deliver high quality material on time.

EDUCATION

2019 | UX Immersion

CareerFoundry

• Focus on data-driven UX methodology with a comprehensive, hands-on training ranging from user research and user flows to wireframing, prototyping & creating mockups

2014-2016

Entertainment Media Business Certification New York University

2004-2009

Bachelor of Arts Degree in Communications William Paterson University

WORK EXPERIENCE

Video Editor

T.S Creative, 2013-Present

- •Conduct initial client consultation to determine client needs
- Produce creative promo videos for brands and businesses
- Develop project outline and video treatment for clients

Video Editor

Lindsay Adler Photography, 2013-Present

- Create social media ads for the Lindsay Adler Brand
- Collaboratively manage and oversee video projects

Pharmacy Technician

Stop and Shop Pharmacy, 2003 -2016

- Accurately and efficiently prepared prescription orders
- Interacted with patients and discussed their questions or concerns regarding their medication
- •Trained pharmacy interns how to use pharmacy computer system

SKILLS

User Research
Wireframes
Prototyping
User Flows
Alexa Voice Design
Basic HTML
Time Management
Customer Service
Training &
Managing others
Working
Independently

TOOLS

Sketch
Basalmiq
Marvel
Figma
Usercrowd
Adobe Creative Suite
Frame.io

HOBBIES

Cycling Learning useful programs